(Previously)
Why aren't you asleep yet?
Getting some water.
Do you want some?
Then grab one for me, thanks.
Why aren't you asleep?
Can't sleep. Scrolling on my phone.
I want to secretly ask you,
just
today,
my one vote today,
did you vote for me or...?
You mean tonight?
Yes.
Can I say this?
Just say it secretly.
No one's around anyway.
They're all asleep.
I wasn't, originally,
it's just...
(Episode 6: Thermal Contrast
Eruption)
I don't know if I can say this,
the first day I came here,
and there's that
interview on the first day,
they asked at the beginning,
you know, who
you most want to get to know.
I wrote your name.
Really?
(Beaming with Joy)
Is that true or not?
Really? You're not lying to me, are you?
Really.
Because
I don't know, actually I'm...
the kind of person who
goes by first impressions.
And because
when I came in yesterday,
you said you're also from Guangdong,
and you're also a Scorpio,
and I felt like
I think it's just first feeling.
Mainly it's...
I think it's hard to put into words.
OK, then I know.
OK.
The reason I didn't vote for you today
is
because I really felt
sorry for my roommate.
Because my roommate
just because
these past two days
might have been a bit...
I mean...
It's fine.
Actually it's okay.
It's not because of him,
I just wanted to ask.
And that...
Because he and I,
because tonight he also
that
there was that trust challenge, right?
And he also trusted me a lot.
And I also...
these past few days of getting along with him
I was also very happy, because we
can chat a lot together.
He's a good friend.
Because you saw tonight,
he
might have
during Truth or Dare was a bit...
I understand, because he,
because Tyler is indeed
quite sensitive.
And I actually
felt he wasn't very happy yesterday.
Yes,
we chatted yesterday and...
Anyway, today I really felt sorry for him.
Just him.
Then why didn't you
ever ask me
why didn't I vote for you before?
Why didn't you ask?
Is it that you don't really
you don't really care,
or what?
No, I think
actually.
Because the first day was
the first day, everyone just arrived,
and we weren't really close.
And on the first day,
there was that situation.
When I was cooking,
at that time I asked
CH to help me cut vegetables.
And he accidentally cut
accidentally cut his hand. Yes.
And I felt really guilty.
I felt so sorry for him.
So you voted for him out of guilt, right?
Was it out of guilt?
Yes.
Really?
Really.
So these two days
were all friendship votes?
Yes, and the second day was because
we chose partners for the photo shoot.
And.
I felt
that I worked pretty well with him,
so I gave my vote to him.
So.
Because I feel like these
past few days we haven't
just
had much chance to work together or
the opportunities haven't been many.
Yes, but this afternoon
we did had a chance.
But today I originally
originally I felt very
embarrassed, just
I actually wanted to vote for you, but
I still felt
I still felt sorry for my roommate, so.
OK.
So this afternoon you chose me on purpose,
right?
I did this afternoon.
I did it because
the reason I did it this afternoon.
OK, I was going to say
you chose me for the hardest game.
Now I feel a bit better.
No, I thought that
game was simple at first.
That's how it is.
You specifically wanted
to give me an easy way out.
I thought I could get it done quickly,
OK.
So you
don't want to know
why I didn't vote for you?
Do you want to know?
Anyway, they're all asleep.
If you want, you can say it.
I'll listen.
They're all asleep.
I'll tell you secretly.
It's because.
Here's the thing.
Because I just arrived,
and I wasn't familiar with everyone.
And I felt that since...
I'm sharing a room with Joel, I thought,
I'll vote for my roommate.
That way we'd both
be happier.
I was afraid if he got zero votes,
he'd be mad at me.
Yes, so I voted for him.
The first day I voted for him.
So on the first day, when you
didn't get any votes,
I actually felt very
a bit,
actually I regretted it a little.
I think I should have voted for you.
I was really afraid you'd feel hurt.
The second day I had a reason too.
And I thought, you're already like this,
everyone will definitely vote for you.
Everyone will definitely vote for you.
If I also vote for you,
you wouldn't know it was me anyway.
So I might as well not flatter myself.
Not overthink it, right?
So I still voted for Joel.
That way he'd be happier too.
So the second day I voted for Joel again.
Actually, both days my main reason
was friendship.
Yes, friendship votes.
Just a roommate bond.
But what you told me today,
that it's because of friendship votes,
then I think maybe tomorrow
if you want,
I think we can
do like today.
I think we can...
I haven't even said I
want to invite you to,
Go complete a task together or?
If tomorrow I think
if there is
some kind of collaborative task,
I think we can.
OK, then
tomorrow aren't you still going to
get up and make breakfast for everyone?
Then I want to do it with you.
Is that okay?
I want to be with you.
Sure.
Really?
OK.
You still want to eat beef?
You remember I like beef.
But you probably can't eat spicy food.
(Sweet Contentment)
Right.
Then I think tomorrow morning we can make
a non-spicy beef sandwich.
OK, then
let's do it together tomorrow, okay?
Then tomorrow
around...
we'll see.
If you can't get up,
I'll never make it for you again.
Alright then, let's sleep.
OK, let's go up and sleep.
OK, I'm going first, I'm off.
Good night.
Let's go eat.
Another beautiful day.
Take our seats.
We came down so early?
Pretty hearty breakfast here.
Nice.
This breakfast looks quite good.
Hello, good morning.
Morning.
So lavish today.
Millet porridge.
Sit down.
Steamed buns.
No need.
I don't want this.
How did you sleep?
Not bad.
Slept pretty well.
What time did you go to bed?
Not early anyway.
Then everyone probably wasn't early.
Probably fell asleep after three.
Late.
What time did you get up today...
I got up pretty early today.
Then did you take a nap?
Yeah.
What time did you sleep last night?
3:30.
Just couldn't sleep.
Just thinking.
Thinking about tomorrow.
Thinking about what will happen tomorrow?
All 3:30.
Because we stayed too
late at the beach last night,
so I couldn't get up this morning.
And I didn't get to do it with him,
that sandwich-making plan.
That day I asked if everyone drinks coffee,
and you said you don't have that habit.
So I ordered one for myself,
and for
Tyler too.
So tired.
So tired, right?
So delicious.
Fried meat patty.
Come to my bowl.
Is there no tissue here?
Didn't we bring some at first?
After using it, I'll go
upstairs to get some.
I'll go get a pack of tissues.
I'm done.
I don't want to eat anymore, I'm full.
You're full?
I'm full.
I'm going to do the next move.
Finished so fast?
I'm done.
Because I'm going to
draw.
I'm going to put your
little portrait on our board.
So do you have any rules?
No.
You need to come up with one.
I have to think of one?
No limits also counts.
No, we already have two.
Then,
is it just, like,
roommate rules,
about daily life?
Anything, up to you.
So hard to think of.
It's fine, I'll draw while you think.
OK.
It's fine.
Then I'll draw you.
Anyone still eating this?
I'll eat it.
You eat this.
Then you eat.
You eat.
Eat if you want.
I'll draw you here.
Let's each tear half.
OK.
I suggest we have this again tomorrow.
Alan.
Turn around so I can see.
He looks a bit chill today.
OK, done.
You're so good.
You can draw.
No, I'm just
suddenly wanting to eat something
with some flavor.
You're drawing again?
Yeah, I'll just add Alan in too.
I can feel what you mean
about this egg being hard to peel.
Mine is especially hard too.
That one is super hard to peel, really.
Let's see.
So your seventh rule is...
Which one is me?
Can you help me wash this?
Sure, just put it here.
I'll wash it for you.
Thanks.
Write...
"Don't shower for too long."
OK.
Joel.
Looks so much like him.
Such a good hype man.
Really looks like him.
Awesome.
Alan.
We each have that crush gift.
Your crush gift,
where is it?
We all put them over there.
OK.
I'll bring it down.
Do you want to bring yours over?
Let's put them together over there.
OK, sure.
Then mine can be
put there together.
Really looks like him.
I feel like you're really
good at catching details.
You're so good.
So good at giving hyping me up.
No, this part looks just like him.
Let me put it for you.
Thanks.
Let's wait until I finish drawing
this and put them together.
Together?
Yeah, then we can take a Polaroid later.
Let me put it over there for Alan first.
Then we'll take the photo later.
Sure.
Do you know each of our crush gifts?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You can guess.
Come on, guess our crush gifts.
Then I know two.
This is you.
Is this yours?
No, this isn't mine.
There was a little hint yesterday.
When we were playing Truth or Dare.
Yeah, it's... you told me.
Whose is this?
This is.
Is this yours?
This is mine. (skateboard)
Then what about this?
This lollipop is...
This is very obvious.
Who likes candy?
It's Tyler.
Tyler.
And this palette.
I think the palette doesn't need...
The palette is.
Elio's.
So by elimination, this...
Who else?
This is Young's.
Because he has that cat,
and he braids it into a bracelet,
braids it into a cord.
Like this.
YEAH.
And this side is ours.
Later we can take some photos
and stick them all up here.
Yeah, we can take a group photo together.
Young.
Hang it here.
You can come down now.
Young?
Every day he's
elusive.
Young is probably in the bathroom.
I don't know.
Bathroom.
Yes.
Are there dumbbells here?
Put it here.
That one fell over.
Which one? Help me fix it.
Done?
Let me see.
Done.
Are you done here?
Finished.
OK, then let's
come over and take a Polaroid.
Sure.
We have a new friend joining us.
I'm coming.
Coming.
That one seems broken.
Is this broken?
Yes.
Let's try taking one first.
Let's try.
Sure.
It seemed broken the past two days.
You shoot that one.
Because there are seven tokens now.
Let me try to see if it works.
Probably there was no film yesterday.
Let's see if this one works.
If it works,
then it's fine.
Then come over.
Probably can't get the whole view.
Selfie?
I don't think we can get it all.
Then someone still needs to.
Can it self-timer? No.
How about Tyler holds it?
OK, I'll hold it.
Come on.
Let's just make do.
Three.
Two.
One.
OK.
Let me look at these.
Good.
Pretty good, let me see the previous ones.
Taken in the car.
Here.
OK.
Then I'll go.
It's the doorbell.
I'll get it.
OK.
So cringe.
No one curious?
I'm back.
What?
So big this time.
YEAH.
Acting audition.
Today is Acting Trial Day.
All contestants form teams freely,
divided into three groups.
Each group must complete a short play
and perform on stage in turn.
After all performances,
voting will be done by group.
Each group holds one vote,
and cannot vote for their own group.
The group with the most votes wins.
All members of the winning group will have
priority in choosing scripts and
roles in the final graduation play.
I have character profiles here.
And we
rubbing hands together in anticipation.
It's free choice,
pick a role you want.
Then you automatically match.
Automatically match?
Yes, it's him.
We don't know the play yet,
but inside are scattered roles.
Then you pick one role
and with another person, it forms
a CP pair.
Yes.
Then we perform together,
collaborate on a play.
Yes.
So today we finally enter
our
actor trial segment.
Yeah, let's look at the profiles first.
Waner.
Coming.
Let's see what roles there are.
A young man from a small town.
A person afraid of choices
has two people in his heart.
Controlling personality.
OK.
Let me see.
I've chosen.
So fast, wait.
I haven't finished looking.
I'll take this one.
I think this is great.
This one is very short.
Just these two words.
I'm done.
A man surnamed Han.
I'm OK too.
I'm kind of leaning toward
I want to choose Shen Yuan.
I want to choose Jiang Hai.
I want to choose.
Because I think I like
I know, I'll choose the man surnamed Han.
Because I'm a controlling personality,
I like to take the initiative.
I also like Shen Yuan, to be honest.
Then you two fight over it.
I like Jiang Hai.
I'm also
a controlling type.
What are you two arguing about?
We both want to choose Shen Yuan.
Because I think this suits me better.
I want the man surnamed Han.
I think this is
I also choose Shen Yuan.
Just kidding.
You choose someone else.
I choose.
Let me take another look.
You choose Jiang Yuan.
We're both Yuan, is that okay?
I don't want, let me see.
OK.
You're Jiang Yuan?
No.
Jiang Hai.
I choose Lin Shi.
Won't be rejected.
If you don't fight, you won't...
This is quite.
Don't steal mine, I've chosen.
I won't steal, I just want Shen Yuan.
OK.
I want the man surnamed Han.
OK, got it.
Sit.
I choose Wen Ming.
Then it's basically us.
Then I'll choose Ye Qisheng.
Even though the paper's all picked over,
It's fine, let me look, just curious.
Ye Qisheng.
Thanks.
It's fine.
The back side is all good.
You gave me the Shen Yuan role.
I didn't see the back just now.
The first page.
Lin Shi, Jiang Yuan.
Shen Yuan.
Jiang Hai.
Man surnamed Han.
No, you're really called
'Man surnamed Han'?
Han Tong.
I thought it was literally
'Man surnamed Han'.
Ye Qisheng.
Ye Qisheng sounds exactly
like a domineering CEO.
Martial arts cultivation novel.
No, like a domineering CEO.
[Elio's character: Guarded
and aloof. Waner's character:
Gentle but can't make a choice.
CH's: Controling and proactive]
[Tyler's: Avoidant but passionate.
Young's: Uses comedy to hide sincerity]
[Alan's: Confident and direct
after experiencing regret.
Joel's: Stable but terrified
of not being picked]
Before you studied acting,
did you have any warm-ups?
Yes, we do some
like improvisation exercises.
What improvisation?
Scene sketches,
character profiles,
just very improvisational performances.
It's like doing actor training exercises.
Called improv.
Unleashing nature.
Then will you teach us?
We can try doing some
improv exercises.
OK.
Sure.
Then I'll go get that
improv notebook.
Then everyone write down
what we're going to do, okay?
OK.
Wait for me.
Coming, two huge markers.
Oh my god.
Are there topics on these?
No, we write them ourselves.
Each person writes one.
Each writes one.
One on each sheet.
One question per sheet.
Then, because we'll have seven questions,
seven people.
Then we'll flip them.
Yes, randomly.
Whatever we flip, we play.
We probably just need to do one question.
And we can split into groups,
three groups, with 2-2-3 people.
Just to complete this one question.
That works too.
And we can
for example, within a certain question,
like having a set premise.
We can prepare a few keywords,
for example,
like singing.
You need to incorporate singing
naturally into the scene.
Something like that.
We can split into three groups,
and
add a keyword into
the given premise,
and complete the
keyword within that premise.
Then you write the first one.
OK, I'll write first.
I'll write...
You two don't look yet.
This is the topic I thought of.
Running into your ex after breaking up.
OK.
So tricky.
Then let me ask,
so I need to use this.
No need.
Just play yourself.
Everyone can form teams freely.
Anyone want to claim this one?
Not claim,
you have to perform it.
We can think about it first.
Then we can decide on three keywords.
Let's brainstorm.
Keywords.
I'll go.
It can be
if anyone thinks of
something, add it directly.
Then pick your own teammates,
pick your own keywords.
Wait, I thought of one.
Hug.
Each other.
Then do I write on this page again?
You can flip to the next page.
He said 'meet in the bathroom'?
I'll just write 'dance'.
I won't pick this one.
Then we'll go with this.
Then you pick.
I don't want.
Actually I was thinking of push-ups.
But doing push-ups in
the bathroom is weird.
Dancing in the bathroom
isn't normal either.
Let's show everyone.
OK.
First keyword is 'hug each other'.
Very normal.
Second keyword is
'meeting in the bathroom'.
Meeting in the bathroom.
Third keyword is 'dance'.
How about this?
Let's be fair in forming teams.
We'll...
Does everyone want to
draw lots or choose freely?
Let's draw.
You want to draw?
Yes, I think
drawing lots is better.
OK, then write on a paper and
then we draw.
Drawing lots?
Yes, drawing lots.
Then I'll write one, two, three.
Those who draw one,
two, and three
will be automatically
split into three groups.
Two ones, two twos, three threes.
OK, you write.
And the keywords will also be
one, two, three, then draw the first one.
Yes, that works.
No need for random picking, for fairness.
A bit fair.
OK, no problem.
Confused about my future.
First draw partners,
then draw topics.
Come on.
One by one.
Start from this side.
Start from that side.
I became the last.
Because he started from that side.
This one.
Which one do you choose?
You choose, I'll take this.
Don't be too nervous now,
it's just choosing teammates.
Not choosing topics.
Come on, three, two, one, reveal together.
I'm three.
I'm one.
I'm two.
I'm three.
I'm one.
I'm two.
The three of us are three.
The three of us.
OK.
You two are
two.
One, two.
We two.
OK then.
Then is it.
OK, let's start drawing.
Give me a one and a two.
Give me two, and then give me a one.
Then start drawing topics.
Each group sends a representative to draw.
The keywords for groups one, two, three.
OK, you come.
I don't want to draw 'dance'.
Is my hand unlucky?
Let each group send one rep. Come on.
OK.
Then you come.
I'm Waner.
I'll let Waner come.
Waner come.
Which of you two?
Young come.
Then you three come.
Us three.
If I draw 'dance' will you be mad?
Probably not.
It's fine, just go with it.
We just need to see who gets 'dance'.
Three.
Didn't you write this yourself?
It's fine.
(Digging His Own Grave)
Let's dance.
First is 'hug each other'.
Yes, ours is so simple.
I saved myself.
Let's discuss.
Discuss how to perform.
OK.
How do we discuss this?
Come try.
No, we can draw
draw one, two, three.
Sure.
Are you all ready?
I'll do it.
Oh no.
Probably not.
Really one.
(Too Scared to Look)
I'll take three.
Come on.
Let's dance together.
Let me go to the audience.
Come on, come on.
Actors, take your places.
(The Warm-up Quiz Begins!)
It's been a long time since we separated.
How have you been lately?
Not bad.
But if you ask if I'm doing great,
not really.
And you?
Where did you go after graduation?
I'm also fine.
Paid off debts,
got a job.
Just
some things I used to have are gone.
It's in the past.
All past.
Let's dance.
Shall we?
Let's go.
Aren't you going to take my hand?
If you invite me to dance,
you have to lead me.
After all these years,
you still remember this dance.
Thank you.
Actually.
It's fine.
Goodbye.
Great.
Look at my bathroom segment.
Come on, second up.
Come on, the second I
personally gave to you.
Ours is very simple.
We didn't expect your scene to be so long.
Such a complete play.
Yeah.
Our scene is very short.
Our scene is probably.
It feels like he's genuinely shy.
(Overacting)
I can't keep up with this.
Elio and them are quite cute.
Pretty creative.
So cute, I think they're so cute.
Come on, the one I'm
most looking forward to.
The three-person group.
I'm going back.
What are you doing here?
I'm using the bathroom, you?
I came to the mall to buy some things.
Alone?
Came with a friend.
Friend?
He's
waiting for me outside.
Hey, Tyler.
Why aren't you out yet?
I've been waiting for so long.
Uh,
I'm coming out now.
I was just fixing my hair.
OK, I'll come in and see.
No need.
Why aren't you out yet?
Been waiting for you at the door.
It's fine, I'm just fixing my hair.
OK.
Let's go.
I just saw that thing
I've been wanting to buy.
Oh?
Yeah, I was looking at it for a while.
I want to buy it. Want to
come check it out with me?
Sure.
OK.
Sorry, you
are his friend, right?
Yeah, what's up?
My friend.
That's a former colleague of mine.
Just a colleague.
We were...
Just colleagues?
Let's go.
Wait, the look between you two is weird.
Are you really just colleagues?
Really just colleagues.
I'm really just a colleague.
Yes, real colleague.
Let's go.
OK, let's go.
I thought you were going to argue.
I also thought there'd be
some love triangle drama.
How come it's not what I imagined?
The phone call threw me off.
I thought it would
I figured I needed a reason to come in.
It's fine, we didn't communicate well.
We really need to coordinate the blocking.
Like coming in from that side.
Yes, this phone call
and then coming in from behind me.
I'm a bit
I was really panicked at that moment.
I panicked at that phone call,
I was already flustered.
Off track.
OK, it's over.
So let's go prepare for
the afternoon audition.
Sure.
Great, looking forward to it.
Let's go.
Go.
Go change clothes.
I know, I know this.
Elio, are you there?
What's up?
Are you alone?
Me?
Come, sit.
What?
I have some things I want to ask you.
What are you playing?
I'm playing Han Tong / Shen Yuan.
Here's our script.
Did you get your script?
Right here.
OK, and you're with who?
You and who?
Jiang Hai.
Actually I
have some questions for you.
Because you and Tyler
you're in the same room,
you share a space.
And you two might
have been getting along better lately.
What do you want to ask?
Just say it.
No, here's the thing.
I feel
that these past two days, he and I
have been a bit awkward.
I don't know if you've noticed,
I feel a bit awkward.
A bit awkward.
Yes, when talking to him,
he kind of ignores me.
Yes, and I wanted to
know if he told you
why?
Like, what did I do that made him
uncomfortable,
or
made him unhappy.
I'd like to know more about that.
Didn't you shoot photos together yesterday?
Yesterday?
No, the day before yesterday we shot that.
I felt at the time that he
didn't really want to shoot
these photos with me, because.
Why would you think that?
Because when we,
we're acting, you know,
during the photo shoot there
were some eye-contact scenes,
and he would dodge,
and also feeding watermelon,
he seemed a bit reluctant.
Like that.
And I thought at the time
maybe he wasn't willing to
shoot this with me.
So you...
So I
didn't
vote for him.
Yes, I didn't vote for him.
Yes, because I felt
maybe I'm not his type.
And I didn't vote for him. Yes.
I think.
It might be because.
You know, the day before yesterday,
because of that voting thing
the day before yesterday.
I don't know.
Think about it yourself.
Yes, then.
Right.
OK.
Got it? I didn't say anything.
Don't rat me out.
Then today, pretend I was never here.
OK.
Can you help me find out some things?
Alright.
What time are you going down?
Who did you end up pairing with?
Who is Jiang Hai?
Young.
I'm still with Tyler.
How nice.
Let's find a place to rehearse.
Everyone find a spot.
Careful.
This is good.
Let's rehearse here.
Let's go over it first.
Let's run lines.
Let's perform right here.
This is the living room.
OK.
Living room, door.
Everyone hold your scripts for now.
OK.
Come on.
Let's do a table read first.
Yes.
Actually I want to say,
I feel like the phrasing is off.
Let me see how to phrase it.
Maybe we should try this tone.
I think as long as the meaning is right,
we can change the words.
Because this one feels strange to me.
Half of it I wrote clearly.
Anyway, I think
as long as the meaning gets across.
Sure.
Did you memorize the lines?
I memorized my lines.
OK.
Keep memorizing.
What time do we start?
I don't know, I think we start when ready.
So soon?
Wait, you first
I'm squatting on the ground,
and you're sitting
just squatting
I'm leaning against the wall.
We can...
I can just stand in that corner.
That works too.
We can pretend to lean here, right?
Which side of your face looks better?
Both sides look good.
OK, so you.
So you think the other
side doesn't look good?
No, I'm asking which side you prefer.
Which side do you think looks good?
Both look good.
(Emotional Cup: Full!)
(Perfectly Content)
I'm leaning against the wall.
Then I'm holding two bottles
of beer in my hands.
And I watch you pack things.
So I'm packing things.
Then let's add the blocking.
Let's run it again.
I should walk over,
then lean against the wall, that would
make the scene flow better.
At this point I think you should sit down,
because when you hand it to me,
you should be sitting next to me.
But if my...
I feel maybe
because at this moment it's relaxed,
you're handing me a drink,
but I think I still want
to lean against the wall.
And when you look up against the wall,
one high, one low,
our eyes would meet.
If I'm sitting,
it might be eye-level and not as good.
That works too.
I'll lean on the wall and drink.
I said don't thank me, I want to say,
and then you say you
want to say thank you, right?
I don't want a thank you.
I really have to move tomorrow.
Almost, but I think
we can leave it like this.
A bit awkward.
Yeah, I think the main
issue is the movement path.
I think the path isn't
I think I should.
Every time you say 'forget
it', you have something to say.
I need to get closer.
I see.
Let me try again.
Like, I'm drinking here,
and you say 'never mind'.
Then I need to
either sit next to you
I think we can do it like this.
Maybe I'll do it like this.
I've been packing things,
and you can have a movement.
Like you say
I say 'never mind' every time,
and you say
I know.
Then you come over and help me pack.
Then maybe as we pack,
I'll say,
and you say 'I don't want thank you'.
And just at that moment
you're looking at me.
Every time you say 'never mind'
No.
Don't give me that domineering CEO vibe.
Just sit down.
Domineering CEO.
I know, no, I'm like this.
So when we get to that part,
when you're at that part,
you were saying that.
No, I'm not saying I
because I've been packing things,
maybe there's a lot.
Then I say
you say, I say 'never mind'.
Then you don't stare,
you stare at me first, I don't know.
Then you come help me pack.
You get what I mean?
Let's try it.
So at the start,
he and I sit first.
No matter what we're doing,
eating or drinking.
And let's say
we're sitting here.
Let's say we're
we sit first.
Passing by.
I'm sitting here.
Then.
Knock on the door.
Then knock.
Then come in.
Why are you here?
What's wrong?
No, you.
Why are you moving around?
You should stand still
and make eye contact.
When you hear the door,
just walk straight to the door.
Then open it.
The path is.
So we really open the door like this? OK.
OK?
OK, sure.
Knock.
Why are you here?
I was just passing by.
Is it a bad time?
Jiang Yuan, this is.
Ye Qisheng.
I mentioned him before.
The ex, Ye Qisheng.
He's told you about me?
That's good.
Saves me from introducing myself.
When you say this line,
you need to perform an action.
This action is
you walk in,
look around at the furnishings,
see if anything changed
since you were here.
Then pick up this cup
and take a sip.
That's what you need to do
during this line.
OK, sure.
Really?
Really.
But they didn't live here before.
It could be this house,
or not.
If he needs to come in,
doing it like this would be better.
Otherwise if he wants water,
it would be more natural.
OK.
One more time?
Let's try it.
Sure, come on.
Actually I think we have this table here,
we can try it here.
And you can toss some things there.
I'll
I'll come in and face you directly.
OK?
I'll go over there, just the two of us.
Yes, that's what I mean.
Don't laugh.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
You removed my byline again.
The editor-in-chief did.
Stop using the editor as an excuse.
You know best
how much of this book I actually wrote.
You're the one who knows best.
I know a lot of things.
Like why you didn't answer
my calls for three months.
What does that have to do with the byline?
It does.
Wait.
It doesn't.
It does. You said.
Wait a sec.
Let's pick it up again.
You still want to eat beef today?
(Suddenly Off-Topic!)
I said, do you still want beef today?
Yeah, I want beef every day.
OK, since Alan is here today,
I think we can cook tonight.
We should be able to cook.
We can make beef.
If there's beef,
we can make some.
So the first day, what
impression did you have
of us?
I think Tyler,
Tyler is probably the lively type.
Because when I picked his token second,
he came out.
He's the energetic kind.
So why did you choose that token?
Because I thought he
because I also like sweets,
so I wanted to see.
He specially prepared that candy,
I thought maybe he's
turns out he's just
the free-spirited type.
What about you?
You're a very warm,
cheerful,
and also
patient person.
That's it.
Patient.
That's already a lot, okay?
Do you want to hear me praise you?
No.
Do you want to hear it?
Praise you more.
I'm just asking.
I'm afraid if I praise you too much,
you'll get proud.
I'm just asking.
Are you a proactive person or?
I am
I don't know if I'm
proactive or passive.
It depends
on the situation.
Depends on the person.
OK
What does your being proactive look like?
I don't know.
Maybe you'll feel it in a moment.
[Don't think too much about the
bossy CEO's pattern of thinking] OK.
So if you still have feelings for someone,
but you two haven't been in touch,
would you reach out to them?
You wouldn't.
I think if I have
feelings for someone,
I'm not the type
to be super proactive right away.
Actually I might go through
some situations to be alone with them,
gradually getting to know them.
Or send signals
that I might also be interested.
So it's not like
being super proactive from the start.
It's more like
sending signals.
Rest a bit.
I want to go look around over there.
(Weren't You Supposed to Rehearse?)
I think there is
a further understanding.
I can feel that he
just
makes me want to understand
his inner thoughts more.
Because when I first arrived,
I found him quite
lively, he talked a lot.
But after these few days,
including after getting to know him more,
I found he's actually quite steady.
He knows when to speak,
when to do his own thing.
He's someone with
his own thoughts and opinions.
Whoever laughs during the performance,
I will take this bottle
and hit them hard on the head.
I'm not afraid of laughing, right?
I'm afraid of forgetting my lines.
You know?
I'm really scared I'll forget.
I will take this thing
and hit his head hard.
I'm so afraid of forgetting.
Just suddenly getting stuck.
Do you want to sit for a bit?
OK.
Still need to adapt.
It's just that it still feels
like I joined relatively late.
Maybe in the morning,
when chatting with everyone,
I still feel
a little
a bit unsure...
...of what to talk about?
Yeah.
Afraid of offending.
Maybe it's the fear
of suddenly
still not being quite used to chatting.
Here, have some water.
Thanks.
Thanks, Waner.
Then you two chat first.
OK.
(Script Mode: ON!)
I'm on the script,
writing down
some actions, or
my own
added actions, and marking them.
Or highlighting them.
Because when reading the script,
it's easier to see.
And the lines too.
It's a preliminary understanding
of the acting industry, I suppose.
I think you shouldn't
put too much pressure
on yourself.
Everyone is just happy
and working together.
When you're resting alone,
do you ever feel
a bit uncomfortable
or somewhat uneasy?
Because everyone else
maybe a little bit, to be honest.
Yeah, it's like on the first day,
staying by yourself,
maybe there's still a little...
sometimes you want to say something
but there's no one to talk to.
It might feel a little
not
just a tiny bit of disappointment.
Anyway,
if you need anything,
or if you think I can help,
if I can be useful,
just tell me anytime.
What if you lived with me?
Would you be willing?
I can.
OK.
If you really need me,
and Young on his side,
first I need to talk to Young,
then we'll see.
OK, sure.
Anyway, don't feel pressured.
If you have anything
you want to say,
or any honest thoughts,
we can all talk it over.
OK, good.
I'm just afraid you'll have a burden.
OK, let's run through the later
blocking again，OK？.
We can try this.
You from
I take a step forward and say.
What exactly do you want?
What do I want?
I've been thinking for three months.
Thinking about what for three months?
Isn't it your turn to speak?
Is it my turn?
Yes.
Let go.
Isn't it 'let go'?
No.
Didn't I tell you to let go?
Yes, but I can't let go.
I think here,
letting go is good.
What's good about it?
I think just one move is enough.
But if you let go here,
I can't continue my role.
How can't you continue?
You still have.
You can let go now, I said.
And I still have
I said you can.
Not now.
If I let go here,
then I
won't be able to continue.
Then I
I think we two
can just stand and talk.
Listen to yourself, does that make sense?
What do you mean 'does that make sense'?
How doesn't it make sense? I just.
No.
I can't deliver this line.
This line doesn't make sense.
Then let's not do it.
Sorry I just can't stop it.
Come on.
What exactly do you want?
Yes, like that.
Say it.
I forgot.
Sorry.
I forgot again.
(Another bad take)
Let's do it again.
What exactly do you want?
Are you okay?
(Yet another bad take)
It's fine, let's do it again.
What exactly do you want?
What do I want?
Give it some energy.
(Yet another bad take)
OK.
Then hurry up.
I'm not fast enough?
You're too far from me.
I feel like.
What exactly do you want?
Yes.
Like that.
I think that works.
That works.
What exactly do you want?
(Yet another bad take)
Are you trying to knock me over?
Come on.
Three.
Two.
One.
What exactly do you want?
Say something.
Wait a sec, I forgot.
(Yet another bad take)
Again.
Wait a bit, let me check again.
Come on.
What exactly do you want?
That hurts.
Are you okay?
It hurts, it's been many times.
(Next Episode)
He said it's because he feels that you...
It seems like you don't
really feel a spark with him.
So he didn't pick
you over others.
He's talking nonsense.
Really, so.
Really.
Is he an idiot?
I'm thinking about today's thing.
I think he probably doesn't like me.
In three years there wasn't
a shred of news from him.
Just because he says he's sorry,
he thinks he can come back?
There's a lot of chemistry between them.
Yeah, the sexual tension is real.
"Project XY"